<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Virtual Lab</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="omega">Ω</string>
    <string name="resistance_text">R = 1KΩ</string>
    <string name="ohms_introduction">Ohm’s law is the fundamental law of Electrical Engineering. It relates the current flowing through any resistor to the voltage applied to its ends. According to the statement: The current flowing through a constant resistor is directly proportional to the voltage applied to its ends. This article presents the complete Ohm’s law Lab report and various questions regarding the lab. The latter portion simplifies the law for beginners by delineating the absolute basic concepts for beginners.</string>
    <string name="list_component">1. Variable DC Power supply \n2. 1kΩ resistor (Color code Brown, Black, Red, Gold) \n3. Breadboard \n4. Connecting wires (Jumper wires) \n5. Ammeter</string>
    <string name="ohms_steps">1. Implement the circuit on the breadboard as shown in circuit diagram.
        \n2. Initially set the VDC supply to 0 V and note the current on ammeter.
        \n3. Increase the voltage to 1 V, observe the ammeter and note the readings.
        \n4. Repeat the above step for 2 V, 3V … 10 V. Plot a graph for measured readings.
        \n5. Compare the plot with theoretical calculations.</string>
    <string name="pendulum_info">The Pendulum Experiment is an experiment about gravity.</string>
    <string name="pendulum_objective">1. pendulum bob  2. A long thread  3. Clamp  4. Stopwatch</string>
    <string name="pendulum_steps">Take the string of the pendulum and cut off about 20cm.  If you are really organized, you can use another length of string from the same roll to make a shorter one.  Take back to the same angle and let it fly.  Take another 20cm off the string, replace and try again.</string>
    <string name="reflection_steps">1- Place the paper on the board and fix
        \n2- Place the mirror vertically on the white sheet of paper and trace its edge.
        \n3- Draw a line at right angles to the edge of the edge of the mirror to act as the normal- ON .
        \n4- Stating with angle i as 30 degree , draw an incident ray and place two pins, P and Q along it as shown
        \n5- With your eyes at position shown, place two other pins R and S to coincide with the images of P and Q as seen in the mirror
        \n6- Remove pins R and S and join the dots left with a straight line 7-Measure and record angle r.
        \n8- Repeat procedure 4,5,6
        and \n7for angles i = 35 degree, 40 degree, 45 degree, 50 degree and 55 degree.</string>
</resources>
